ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Endocrine Disruptors, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 51)
  WNY Environmental Summit, #4480, 9/28/13
- Asbestos, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 52)
  WNYCOSH, #4481, 5/1/13
- Lead Awareness, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 53)
  WNYCOSH, #4482, 5/14/13
- Mold, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 54)
  WNYCOSH, #4483, 5/22/13
- Confined Space, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 55)
  WNYCOSH, #4484, 5/23/13
- Heat Stress; Shiftwork, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 56)
  WNYCOSH, #4485, 5/29/13
- Chemical Hazards, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 57)
  WNYCOSH, #4486, 6/20/13
- Mold, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 58)
  WNYCOSH, #4487, 8/6/13
- Workers Rights/OSHA, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 59)
  WNYCOSH, #4488, 8/22/13
- Breakfast Seminar, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 60)
  Worker Institute, #4489, 10/10/13
- NYSDOL HAB, 2013-2014 (Box 38, Folder 61)
  WNYCOSH, #4490 et al
- Trainer, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 62)
  WNYCOSH, #4490, 8/7-8/13
- Monroe County Dept. of Health, LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 63)
  #4491, 6/20/13, Wheaton
- Monroe County Dept. of Health, LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 64)
  #4492, 7/17/13, Wheaton
- Monroe County Dept. of Health, LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 65)
  #4493, 7/31/13, Wheaton
- Monroe County Dept. of Health, LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 66)
  #4494, 8/5/13, Wheaton
- Monroe County Dept. of Health, LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 67)
  #4495, 8/14/13, Wheaton
- Monroe County Dept. of Health, LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 68)
  #4496, 9/9/13, Wheaton
- Monroe County Dept. of Health, LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 69)
  #4497, 9/23/13, Wheaton
- Monroe County Dept. of Health, LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 70)
  #4498, 10/10/13, Wheaton
- Monroe County Dept. of Health, LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 71)
  #4499, 10/28/13, Wheaton
- Monroe County Dept. of Health, LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 72)
  #4500, 11/4/13, Wheaton
- Monroe County Dept. of Health, LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 73)
  #4501, 11/18/13, Wheaton
- Monroe County Dept. of Health, LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 74)
  #4502, 12/2/13, Wheaton
- Lead Renovator- Initial, 2014 (Box 38, Folder 75)
  Monroe County Dept. of Health, #4505, 1/14/14, Wheaton
- Monroe County Dept. of Health, LRRP- I, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 76)
  #4503, 12/16/13, Wheaton
- Buffalo Schools, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 77)
  WNYCOSH, #4538, 10/23/13
- Buffalo Schools, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 78)
  WNYCOSH, #4539, 10/23/13
- MILR Student- Tech. Asst., 2013 (Box 38, Folder 79)
  Cornell ILR, #4540, 8/23/13
- Computer Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 80)
  WNYCOSH, #4541, 9/13/13
- Computer Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 81)
  WNYCOSH, #4542, 10/11/13
- Process Hazards Analysis, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 82)
  WNYCOSH, #4543, 10/3/13
- Process Hazards Analysis, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 83)
  WNYCOSH, #4544, 10/3/13
- Process Hazards Analysis, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 84)
  WNYCOSH, #4545, 10/9/13
- Process Hazard Analysis, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 85)
  WNYCOSH, #4546, 10/9/13
- Confined Space, 2013 (Box 38, Folder 86)
  WNYCOSH, #4547, 10/29/13
- Computer Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  WNYCOSH, #4548, 12/3/13
- Computer Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  WNYCOSH, #4549, 12/12/13
- Health and Safety Committee Skills, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  WNYCOSH, #4550, 1/23/14
- Confined Space, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  WNYCOSH, #4551, 4/22/14
- Training Skills, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  WNYCOSH, #4552, 6/10-11/14
- Monroe County Water Authority, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  WNYCOSH, #4553, 9/27/13
- Monroe County Water Authority- Office Staff, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  WNYCOSH, #4554, 9/27/13
- Monroe County Water Authority, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  WNYCOSH, #4555, 10/30/13
- Monroe County Water Authority- Office Staff, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  WNYCOSH, #4556, 10/30/13
- Monroe County Water Authority- Shoremont, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  WNYCOSH, #4557, 10/5/13
- Monroe County Water Authority, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  WNYCOSH, #4558, 11/7/13
- Monroe County Water Authority- Office Staff, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  WNYCOSH, #4559, 11/7/13
- Monroe County Water Authority- Shoremont, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  WNYCOSH, #4560, 11/12/13
- Lewiston WWTP- Noise, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  WNYCOSH, #4561, 10/4/13
- Lewiston WWTP- Hazop, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  WNYCOSH, #4562, 11/1/13
- Lewiston WWTP- Personal Protective Equipment, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  WNYCOSH, #4563, 12/2/13
- Bath Veterans Hospital- Asbestos, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  WNYCOSH, #4565, 10/8/13
- Bath Veterans Hospital- Lockout/Tagout, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  WNYCOSH, #4566, 12/10/13
- Bath Veterans Hospital- Hazcom/GHS, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  WNYCOSH, #4567, 1/14/14
- Bath Veterans Hospital- Ergonomics, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  WNYCOSH, #4568, 3/11/14
- Fracking- Silica, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  WNYCOSH, #4569, 10/8/13
- IBEW #97- Conflict Resolution, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  WNYCOSH, #4570, 10/10/13
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  WNYCOSH, #4571, 11/4/13
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  WNYCOSH, #4572, 11/4/13
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  WNYCOSH, #4573, 11/4/13
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  WNYCOSH, #4574, 11/4/13
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  WNYCOSH, #4575, 11/6/13
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  WNYCOSH, #4576, 11/6/13
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  WNYCOSH, #4577, 11/6/13
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  WNYCOSH, #4578, 11/6/13
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  WNYCOSH, #4579, 11/8/13
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  WNYCOSH, #4580, 11/8/13
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  WNYCOSH, #4581, 11/8/13
- Niagara Falls- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  WNYCOSH, #4582, 11/8/13
- Niagara Falls WB- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  WNYCOSH, #4583, 11/19/13
- Niagara Falls WB- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  WNYCOSH, #4584, 11/19/13
- Niagara Falls WB- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  WNYCOSH, #4585, 11/22/13
- Niagara Falls WB- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  WNYCOSH, #4586, 11/22/13
- Niagara Falls WB- Violence, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  WNYCOSH, #4587, 11/22/13
- Erie County- Computer Ergonomics, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  WNYCOSH, #4588, 11/14/13
- Endocrines, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  Daemen College, #4589, 10/2/13
- Hazmat- I, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  IUOE, #4590, 2/6/14
- NYSDOL HAB, 2013-2014 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  IUOE, #4590 et al
- Disaster Site Worker, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  IUOE, #4591, 2/10/14
- Smart System Technology and Commercialization Center, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  WNYCOSH, #4592, 1/10/14
- Smart System Technology and Commercialization Center, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  WNYCOSH, #4593, 1/10/14
- Smart System Technology and Commercialization Center, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  WNYCOSH, #4594, 1/30/14
- Smart System Technology and Commercialization Center, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 48)
  WNYCOSH, #4595, 1/31/14
- Smart System Technology and Commercialization Center, 2014 (Box 39, Folder 49)
  WNYCOSH, #4596, 1/31/14
- Bureau Veritas- Safety Data Sheets, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 50)
  WNYCOSH, #4597, 12/9/13
- Workplace and Community, 2013-2014 (Box 39, Folder 51)
  WNYCOSH-NYCOSH, #4397 et al, Jan. 2013- July 2014
- Bureau Veritas- Safety Data Sheets, 2013 (Box 39, Folder 52)
  WNYCOSH, #4598, 12/11/13
- Costing out the Contract, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 53)
  SEIU Local 121, 08W001, 7/24-25/08, Wheaton
- Sexual Assault, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 54)
  Buffalo News and News Guild, 08W002, 7/8/08, Wheaton
- Advanced Collective Bargaining, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 55)
  Public, 08W003, 8/11-12/08, Wheaton
- Regional Roundtable on Economic Early Alert Lay-off Aversion, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 56)
  Public, 08W005, 7/22/08, Fleron
- Community Collaboration, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 57)
  Urban Economic Development, 08W006, 7/21/08, Fleron
- Successful Supervision, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 58)
  Mentholatum, 08W010, 9/29-30/08, Wheaton
- Civil Rights Committee Training, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 59)
  Republic Engineered Products and the USW, 08W012, 9/10/08, Wheaton
- Steward Training (LB408), 2008 (Box 39, Folder 60)
  Public Workshop, 08W013, 9/21/08, Wheaton
- Contract Administration for Labor and Management, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 61)
  Public, 08W014, 10/20-21/08, Wheaton
- Workplace Harassment, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 62)
  Arcelor Mittal, 08W017, 10/14/08, Wheaton
- Civil Rights Training, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 63)
  Republic Engineered Products, 08W018, 10/29/08, Wheaton
- Performance Appraisals, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 64)
  Mentholatum, 08W019, 11/12/08, Wheaton
- Negotiations and Costing out Contract, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 65)
  UA Local 520, 08W020, 11/12-13/08, Wheaton
- Promoting a Workplace Culture of Mutual Respect, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 66)
  08W021, 1/15-16/09, Wheaton
- GMEECO II Conference, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 67)
  08W022, 11/3-4/08, Wheaton
- Industrial Relations in EU and Other Global and Emerging Economies, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 68)
  082023, 11/27-28/08, Wheaton
- Champions at Work Award, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 69)
  Cameron Compression Systems, 08W300, 8/24/08, Grogan
- Labor Advisory Committee Meeting, 2008 (Box 39, Folder 70)
  08W503, 9/11/08, Wheaton
- NYSUT: Depew Middle School [Folder 1 of 2], 1991 (Box 39, Folder 71)
- NYSUT: Depew Middle School [Folder 2 of 2], 1991 (Box 39, Folder 72)
- NYSUT: Kenmore Middle School [Folder 1 of 2], 1988 (Box 39, Folder 73)
- NYSUT: Kenmore Middle School [Folder 2 of 2], 1988 (Box 39, Folder 74)
- Mutual Gains Refresher, 2010 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  Labor Public, 1/19/10, Wheaton
- Workplace Violence, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  (Professional Development), 6/15/09
- NYS Dept. of Labor HAB, 2009-2010 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- FS February '09, 2009 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- General AIS Information, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- NYS Dept. of Labor HAB, 2008-2009 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Lead Proposals, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  NYC-HPD
- Training Proposal, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  ECC
- Course Approvals/Requests, 1997-1998 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  NYS Dept. of Health/Dept. Environmental Conservation
- Niagara County Community College- Workshop Series (Proposal), 2003 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Monroe County Claim Voucher and Quarterly Billings, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Legislative Initiative, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Legislative Initiative, 2003-2004 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  WNYCOSH-NYS
- Miscellaneous Tech. Asst., 2001-2002 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- OSHA Training Institute Education Centers, 2002 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Health and Safety Program Planning- Albany, 2001-2003 (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Lead and Asbestos Training (Proposal), 2003 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  SUNYAB Center for Integrated Waste Management
- ROCOSH, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- ROCOSH, 2002-2003 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  NYS Dept. of Labor
- NYS Dept. of Labor, 2005-2006 (Box 40, Folder 20)
- WNYCOSH, 2008-2009 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- WNYCOSH- NYSDOL HAB, 2006-2007 (Box 40, Folder 22)
- WNYCOSH- NYS Legislative Initiative (Assembly), 2006-2007 (Box 40, Folder 23)
- WNYCOSH- NYS Legislative Initiative, 2006-2007 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  Volker
- WNYCOSH- NYS Legislative Initiative, 2006-2007 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  Rath
- NYS Dept. of Labor HAB, 2007-2008 (Box 40, Folder 26)
- Special Legislative Grants- WNYCOSH, 2007-2008 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  Rath and Volker
- OSHA Vulnerable Workers Grant, 2007-2008 (Box 40, Folder 28)
- IUOE- Joint Training Fund, 2007-2008 (Box 40, Folder 29)
- Carmi- Faculty Reports, etc., 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 30)
- Program Information Report, 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 31)
- Program Information Report, 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 32)
- Program Information Monthly Report, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 33)
- Strategies for Teaching Health and Safety, 1997-2003 (Box 40, Folder 34)
- Russel Sage, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  8/07
- Sloan, 2006 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  11/06
- Wendt Foundation, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  6/05
- Child Care Coalition, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 38)
- Courses, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 39)
- Blue Sheets M.L., 1994 (Box 40, Folder 40)
- Cash Receipts, 1994-1996 (Box 40, Folder 41)
- Expenses, 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  7/94-6/95
- Mail-in Registrations/Billing, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 43)
- Letters- TKY and Permission Copyright, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 44)
- Mailing Information, 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 45)
- Courses and Outline, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 46)
- Meetings Core Content and Brochure Updates, 1993-1996 (Box 40, Folder 47)
- Annual Reports [Folder 1 of 3], 1986-1999 (Box 40, Folder 48)
- Annual Reports [Folder 2 of 3], 1986-1999 (Box 40, Folder 49)
- Annual Reports [Folder 3 of 3], 1986-1999 (Box 40, Folder 50)
- Grant Documents, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  3/15/04
- Ben Mesler, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Clean and Renewable Energy, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  2/7/08
- Workplace Violence (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Nellie Brown Certificates, 1988-1996 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Correspondence [Folder 1 of 2], 1990-2005 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Correspondence [Folder 2 of 2], 1990-2005 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- News Clippings, 1991-2002 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- OSHA Documents, 2002-2008 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Basic Labor Leadership Skills Workshops, 2013 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Lead Abatement Supervisor Workshops, 2013 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- UAW Food Jobs Safe Jobs, 2004 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- New York City Construction Labor, 2006 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Guidelines on Assessment and Remediation of Fungi in Indoor Environments, 2002 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- US Supreme Court: Exxon v. Baker, 2008 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Finance [Folder 1 of 5], 2008-2009 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Finance [Folder 2 of 5], 2008-2009 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Finance [Folder 3 of 5], 2008-2009 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Finance [Folder 4 of 5], 2008-2009 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Finance [Folder 5 of 5], 2008-2009 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- DEC Data -- [program #3630 - box 27/ff10] (Box 42, Folder 1)